Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Stage projects, 1974-2009
  - Subseries 2.11: The Ring of the Nibelung, 1997-2005
    - Costume design: drawings (binders), circa 1997-1998 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
    - Costume design: drawings (Brünhilde), circa 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Costume design: fitting and development photographs, circa 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 6-7)
    - Costume design: fitting photographs (The Rhinegold), 1997 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      Includes notes and fabric swatches.
    - Costume design: fitting photographs (The Valkyrie), circa 1997 (Box 137, Folder 9-10)
      Includes notes, fabric swatches, and correspondence.
    - Costume design: fitting photographs (Siegfried, Götterdammerung), 1998 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Costume design: fabric samples, circa 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 1, Box 196)
    - Costume design: pattern (Wotan: The Valkyrie), circa 1997-1998 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Production photographs (binder), circa 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 1-4)
      Includes production and costume photographs, transparencies, and slides; also snapshots of Ishioka in Amsterdam.
    - Production photographs, circa 1997-1998 (Box 165, Folder 9, Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Production photographs and costume design drawings (copies) (binders), circa 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 5, Box 139, Folder 1-3, Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Production photographs (contact sheets), circa 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 2-4)
    - Production photographs (transparencies), circa 1997-1998 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - Programs and promotional publications, 1997-1998 (Box 139, Folder 4-7)
    - De Nederlandse Opera season schedules, 1997-1999 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - De Nederlandse Opera newsletters, 1996-2005 (Box 140, Folder 2-3)
    - Posters, 1997-1998 (Box 28)
    - Clippings, 1997-2005, undated (Box 140, Folder 4, Box 153, Folder 4-6, Box 167, Folder 7, Box 704)
  - Subseries 2.12: Varekai (Cirque du Soleil), 2001-2007
    Contains material relating to costume design for Cirque du Soleil production (debuted in Montréal).
    - Scenario and production documents, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Costume design: sketches and drawings, circa 2002 (Box 167, Folder 8-14, Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Costume design: fitting photographs, 2002, circa 2002 (Box 140, Folder 6-7)
    - Costume design: reference book, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Costume design: fabric samples, circa 2002 (Box 192)
    - Production photographs, 2003-2006 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Production slides (binder), circa 2002 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Production/New York slides, 2002 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - Programs, circa 2002 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Publicity and press kits, 2002 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Press review, 2002 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Cirque du Soleil newsletters, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Access badges, circa 2002 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 2002-2007 (Box 154, Folder 2-4, Box 704)
  - Subseries 2.13: Takemitsu: My Way of Life, 2003-2005
    Contains material relating to costume design for musical production that debuted in Berlin, with subsequent performances in Paris and Tokyo. See Series 11 Subseries 11.3 for related audio material.
    - Meeting notes, 2003-2004 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Notebooks, 2003-2004 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Costume design: research clippings and images, circa 2004 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Costume design: sketches and drawings, circa 2004 (Box 168, Folder 1, Box 187)
    - Costume design: development photographs and notes, circa 2004 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Programs (German performance), 2004 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Program and newsletter (French performance), 2005 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Japanese performance), 2005 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Flyers, 2004-2005 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Reviews and clippings, 1996, 2004-2005 (Box 154, Folder 5, Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.14: Hurricane tour (Grace Jones), 2009
    Material relates to costume design.
    - Project binder, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 3-7, Box 143, Folder 1-2)
      Binder includes research clippings, notes, fabric swatches, and copies of drawings and fitting photographs for various costumes. Also includes some correspondence (printed emails), project documents, and song lyrics.
    - Research clippings, song lyrics and notes, 2009, undated (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Costume drawings and sketches, circa 2009 (Box 170, Folder 9-11, Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Publicity and research, 1988, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.15: Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, 2007-2009
    - Project binder, 2007-2009 (Box 143, Folder 3-4)
      Primarily meeting notes and correspondence.
    - Costumes
  - Subseries 2.16: Other projects, 1970-2007
    Primarily stage productions for which Ishioka designed posters.
    - Hair: slides, circa 1970 (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - Hair: poster, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Hair: poster production material, circa 1970 (Box 42)
    - Maboroshi no onna (Theater of Itsuki works): poster, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Maboroshi no onna: poster production material, circa 1973 (Box 48)
    - Kimiko in Seibu, "Stage Design:" slides, 1976 (Box 458)
      Primarily relating to stage design work for jazz singer Kimiko Kasai; also includes some promotional or record cover images.
    - Various stage projects: notes and correspondence, 1996-2007, undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2.17: Unrealized projects, undated
    - Wicked: costume drawings and sketches, circa 2002 (Box 207, Folder 1-3)
    - Criss Angel: costume drawings and sketches, undated (Box 187, Folder 3)
      See Series 11 Subseries 11.3 for related audio material.
    - Unidentified: set sketches and notes, undated (Box 207, Folder 4-5)
  - Subseries 2.18: Unidentified projects, undated
    - Production photographs, undated (Box 204, Folder 3-4)
    - Research clippings and images, undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Stage design: technical drawings Staatsoper Wien (Vienna), 1984 (Box 596)
    - Fabric samples, undated (Box 196)
- Series 3: Moving image projects, 1980-2012
  Series contains material relating to Ishioka's film, video, and television projects. Material documenting Bram Stoker's Dracula (Francis Ford Coppola, 1992) includes costume design drawings and posters created by Ishioka for the film's Japanese release. There is little original material for other film projects. Posters designed by Ishioka for the Japanese release of Apocalypse Now are in Subseries 3.10.
  Audiovisual material relating to Ishioka's film projects Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters and Bram Stoker's Dracula is located in Series 11.
  This series also contains items pertaining to the video projects Bagunça and Mechanisms of Density: The Last Word from Paradise (Pat Metheny). Audiovisual material for these projects as well as for the video "Cocoon" (Björk) is in Series 11.
  Related materials
  See the Eiko Ishioka papers at the Margaret Herrick Library, Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences for additional film-related material.
  - Subseries 3.1: Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, 1985
    - Production images: slides and transparencies (binder), circa 1985, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 5-6)
    - Press kit and stills, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
    - Cannes Film Festival programs, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1985 (Box 704)
  - Subseries 3.2: Bram Stoker's Dracula, 1992-1993
    Material documenting Ishioka's costume design work for Bram Stoker's Dracula (Francis Ford Coppola, 1992), including costume drawings and posters created by Ishioka for the film's Japanese release. Drawings are mostly in color; many have annotations. Also present are snapshots from awards events. See Series 11 for related audiovisual material, including recorded conversations with director Francis Ford Coppola.
    Posters in boxes in 297-298 are housed onsite at YRL.
    - Costume design: drawings, circa 1992; 113-114 are map folders (Box 113, Box 114, Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Costume design: drawings (slides), undated (Box 459, Folder 1, Box 492)
    - Poster: red robe, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Poster: title, red with black lettering (vertical), 1992 (Box 6)
    - Poster: title, red with black lettering (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 297)
    - Poster: title, red with black lettering "Dr" (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 297)
    - Poster: title, red with black lettering "acula" (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 297)
    - Poster: eye with title (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 296)
    - Poster: eye (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 296)
    - Poster: couple Medusa, Werewolf (vertical), 1992 (Box 6)
    - Poster: couple Medusa, Werewolf (oversize, horizontal), 1992 (Box 298)
    - Poster: triptych of couple Medusa, Werewolf (2 vertical, 1 horizontal), 1992 (Box 298)
    - Print (poster image: couple Medusa, Werewolf) (Box 114)
    - Poster: U.S. release, version 1 (not EI design), 1992 (Box 6)
    - Poster: U.S. release, version 2 (not EI design), 1992 (Box 6)
    - Academy/Independent Spirit Awards: event photographs, circa 1993 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Negatives (costume/poster images), undated (Box 144, Folder 5, Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Publicity and clippings, 1992-1993, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 6, Box 518, Folder 1)
    - Award, circa 1993 (Box 720)
      Wooden, signed "award" commemorating Ishioka's Oscar; includes signatures from Misa, Brigit Roberto, Emiko Kaji, Akira, Tony Erpelding, Sharon Polledri, Steve Jobs, Lori Barnett, Satjin Chahil, Albert Chi, Gina and Mike Cerre.
  - Subseries 3.3: The Cell, 2000
    - Promotional booklet (Japanese), 2000 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Poster, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Subseries 3.4: The Fall, 2006
    - Promotional booklet (Japanese), 2007 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3.5: Mirror Mirror, 2012
    - Costume design: sketches, circa 2010 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Publicity (swag bag with book), circa 2012 (Box 707)
  - Subseries 3.6: Bagunça, 1980-1984
    Primarily photographs and slides taken in Brazil, most likely related to the video project Bagunça that Ishioka worked on with musician Sadao Watanabe and photographer Kazumi Kurigami. See Series 11 for related audio material. Empty VHS boxes for the project are in box 246.
    - Brazil photographs (snapshots), 1980 (Box 151, Folder 11, Box 715, Folder 5)
    - Brazil slides (binders), 1980, circa 1980 (Box 380, Folder 1, Box 468, Folder 6, Box 469, Folder 1-5, Box 494)
      Binders also include transparencies and negatives. Binder in box 494 has slide stills from video.
    - Publicity, 1980 (Box 517, Folder 2)
    - Poster, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Subseries 3.7: Mechanisms of Density: The Last Word from Paradise (Pat Metheny video), 1995
    See Series 11 for related audiovisual material. LaserDisc version of video is in box 178.
    - Storyboards and notes (in Japanese), 1994, circa 1995 (Box 144, Folder 9-10)
    - Photographs, transparencies, negatives, 1994 (Box 469, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3.8: Faerie Tale Theatre: "Rip Van Winkle" episode, circa 1987 (Box 715, Folder 14)
    Polaroid photographs of television screen taken while viewing episode. See Series 11 for related video material.
  - Subseries 3.9: Other projects
    Subseries contains posters Ishioka designed for other films and related material.
    Oversize posters in boxes 291-292 are housed onsite at YRL.
    - Akira Kurosawa Whole Picture: poster, circa 1973 (Box 1)
    - Apocalypse Now (helicopters): poster (oversize, horizontal), 1979 (Box 292)
    - Apocalypse Now (Brando): poster (oversize, horizontal), 1979 (Box 292)
    - Apocalypse Now: poster production material (Box 291)
    - Apocalypse Now: posters on display (slides), 1980 (Box 459, Folder 2-3)
    - L'Innocente: poster (oversize, horizontal), 1978 (Box 295)
    - L'Innocente: poster production material, undated (Box 48)
    - L'Innocente: slides, 1978 (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - Koyaanisqatsi: poster (oversize, horizontal), 1983 (Box 295)
    - Koyaanisqatsi: publicity, undated (Box 517, Folder 1)
    - Marlene: poster (various sizes), undated (Box 15)
    - Mio: poster, 1971 (Box 16)
    - The Morning Schedule: poster, 1972 (Box 16)
    - The Morning Schedule: photographs and contact sheets, circa 1972 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - The Morning Schedule: transparencies, undated (Box 450, Folder 6)
    - Trois Couleurs Bleu: poster, undated (Box 36)
    - Portfolio: Mio, Morning Schedule, 1970s (Box 497)
      Includes slides, transparencies, and film.
- Series 4: Exhibitions and events, 1966-1992
  Series consists of material relating to Ishioka's involvement in artistic exhibitions, especially those she curated in Tokyo about the German filmmaker and photographer Leni Riefenstahl (1980, 1992) and the Walker Art Center installation, Tokyo: Form & Spirit (1986). Also present are numerous posters created by Ishioka for display in or to advertise various exhibitions and events, mostly in Japan. A small amount of material documents the 1990 AIDS benefit, Aid & Comfort II.
  See Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
  - Subseries 4.1: Leni Riefenstahl exhibitions, 1980-circa 2008
    Material in this series relates to two exhibitions curated by Ishioka in Tokyo of Leni Riefenstahl's life and work: Nuba (1980) and Life (1992). Items are primarily multiple sets of photographic copies of images used in the exhibitions. Material also includes framed exhibited images from Life, posters for both projects, and images of the exhibits and of Ishioka with Riefenstahl. See Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
    Some images from the Life exhibition may have also been used in Ishioka's 1979 More magazine article "Leni Riefenstahl: The Eternal Woman" (see Series 12) or the Life book that accompanied the exhibition.
    - Life: biographical and early career photographs, circa 1992 (Box 115, Box 145, Folder 1-6, Box 156, Folder 6, Box 173, Folder 9, Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Life: underwater photographs, circa 1992 (Box 116, Box 145, Folder 7-9, Box 146, Folder 1-8, Box 156, Folder 7)
      Includes several sets of images.
    - Life: underwater photographs (slides), circa 1992 (Box 448, Folder 1-3)
    - Life: slides, transparencies, photographs (binders), circa 1992 (Box 445, Box 446)
    - Life: exhibition photographs (framed) (Box 745, Box 746, Box 747, Box 748, Box 749, Box 750, Box 751, Box 752, Box 753, Box 754, Box 755)
      Scope and Contents
      There are two frames in each box.
    - Life: posters, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Life: poster production material, undated (Box 46)
    - Nuba: photographs, circa 1980 (Box 117, Box 184, Folder 2, Box 290)
      May have been used in Life exhibit.
    - Nuba: photographs signed by LR, circa 1980 (Box 172, Folder 1, Box 290)
    - Nuba: slides, transparencies, negatives (binders), circa 1980 (Box 447)
    - Nuba: posters, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Nuba: posters (no text), 1980 (Box 15)
    - Nuba: poster/book jacket production material, undated (Box 47)
    - Images of exhibitions: photographs, circa 1980, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 9, Box 147, Folder 1)
      Primarily slides, negatives, and contact sheets of both exhibitions, including displays and events.
    - Images of exhibitions: slides, circa 1980, 1992 (Box 448, Folder 4-5)
    - Ishioka with Riefenstahl: photographs, 1980-circa 2008 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Publicity, 1992, 2002 (Box 518, Folder 2-3)
    - Books (signed by Riefenstahl) (Box 543)
  - Subseries 4.2: Tokyo: Form & Spirit, 1985-1987
    Contains material relating to the multi-media art installation Tokyo: Form & Spirit, first exhibited at the Walker Art Center, Minneapolis. See also Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
    - Exhibit plans, 1985, undated (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
    - Production photographs (binder), circa 1986 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      Includes photograph copies, transparencies and slides.
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1986 (Box 461, Folder 6-7)
    - Promotional material: Minneapolis, Walker Art Center, 1986 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Promotional material: San Francisco, New York, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1986 (Box 517, Folder 1)
    - Shopping bags, circa 1986 (Box 197)
    - Notes/ sketch (empty slide binder), 1987 (Box 467, Folder 6)
    - Poster (Form and Flower), 1986 (Box 9)
  - Subseries 4.3: Aid & Comfort II, 1990
    Material relates to the benefit concert and culinary event for people fighting AIDS organized by San Francisco area restaurants, hotels, and the University of California at Berkeley, held September 22, 1990.
    - Event photographs, 1990, undated (Box 147, Folder 6-8, Box 157, Folder 3, Box 715, Folder 1)
      Includes snapshots and slides.
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1990 (Box 461, Folder 8)
    - Poster, circa 1990 (Box 1)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 39)
  - Subseries 4.4: Other projects, 1966-1990
    Primarily posters and related material created by Ishioka on commission to advertise various exhibitions and events. Also present are several posters created for display in design exhibitions including Crystal Silence series (Graphic Image '74: Word + Image at the Tokyo Central Museum of Art), Don't Stare at the Poster; Be a Poster (Media Art at the Seibu Museum of Art), and Holiday (Japan Design Committee invitational exhibition).
    See also Series 12. Career: Portfolios (posters) for images of posters.
    - 10th International Biennial Exhibition of Prints in Tokyo: poster, 1976 (Box 1)
    - AMPO-1970-EXPO: posters (Box 1, Box 2)
    - AMPO-1970-EXPO: poster production material, circa 1970 (Box 39)
    - Beyond Japan: transparencies (binders), circa 1991 (Box 461, Folder 9)
      Ishioka had items in this exhibition.
    - Close Up of Japan (Canada Japan Society et al): posters, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Close Up of Japan: slides and transparencies (Box 494)
    - Close Up on Japan: poster production material, undated (Box 39)
    - Crystal Silence No. 3 (oshiri): poster, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Crystal Silence No. 5 (torso): poster, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Crystal Silence (silver drop): poster, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Crystal Silence (avocado): poster, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Crystal Silence series: posters (signed copies), 1974 (Box 4)
    - Crystal Silence series: oshiri image (small poster, signed), 1974 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Crystal Silence series: oshiri image (small foam poster, signed to Grace Jones), undated (Box 744)
    - Crystal Silence series: poster production material, photos, undated (Box 40, Box 349, Folder 8, Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Crystal Silence series: slides and transparencies, undated (Box 494)
    - Don't Stare at the Poster; Be a Poster: poster, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Don't Stare at the Poster; Be a Poster: slides and transparencies, undated (Box 452)
    - Eiko Night banner, undated (Box 738)
      This box also contains an oversize sketch of dancers.
    - Electromagica: poster, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Electromagica: slides (binder), circa 1969 (Box 497)
    - Expo '70: poster, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Expo '70: poster production material, undated (Box 42)
    - George Szell Cleveland Orchestra: poster, undated (Box 9)
    - Habitat (exhibit): poster, undated (Box 9)
    - Hiroshima Appeals: poster, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Holiday (girls with planes): poster, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Holiday (girl with fish): poster, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Holiday: poster production material, undated (Box 43, Box 349, Folder 2)
    - ID For Man (Third Design Conference of JIDA): poster, circa 1968 (Box 10)
    - Ingot (Toshiyuki Kita): poster, undated (Box 10)
    - Ingot (Masayuki Kurokawa): poster, undated (Box 10)
    - Ingot (Shiro Kuramata): poster, undated (Box 10)
    - Ingot: photographs, undated (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - International Canvas Furniture Design Competition: poster, 1973 (Box 10)
    - International Canvas Furniture Design Competition: poster production material, undated (Box 43)
    - International Canvas Furniture Design Competition: slides and transparencies, circa 1973 (Box 454)
    - Japan Shop: poster, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Japan Shop: poster production material, undated (Box 44)
    - Life (exhibit): poster, undated (Box 15)
    - Mitsuko Uchida piano recital: poster, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Morisawa Award International Typeface Competition '84: poster, 1984 (Box 16)
    - New Music Media: poster, 1974 (Box 16)
    - New Music Media 2 in Tsumagoi: poster, 1976 (Box 16)
    - New Music 2 in Tsumagoi: photographs, circa 1976 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Power Now: photograph, circa 1968 (Box 351, Folder 1)
      Image for poster in "War, Protest and Freedom" exhibition, Gallery Nippon.
    - Seibu exhibit (Hiroyuki Itsuki, Eiko Ishioka): poster, undated (Box 30)
    - Seibu: poster production material, undated (Box 56)
    - Shop System Show, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Summer Grand Concert Saburo Kitajima: poster, undated (Box 32)
    - Tokyo Animation Festival '66: poster, 1966 (Box 33)
    - Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques: poster, 1984 (Box 36)
    - Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques: transparencies, undated (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques: postcards, circa 1984 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Unless Peace Comes (exhibit?): poster, undated (Box 37)
    - What is not Strange? (exhibit): poster, undated (Box 37, Box 744)
      Mounted version in gray in box 744.
- Series 5: Fashion and uniforms, circa 1971-2008
  This series consists of a variety of material relating to Ishioka's work with the fashion designer Issey Miyake in the 1970s, and to her design work for the Houston Rockets NBA team. A small amount of material is also present documenting the uniforms designed by Ishioka for Winter Olympics athletes in 2002, and to the opening ceremony of the 2008 Summer Olympics in Beijing.
  - Subseries 5.1: Issey Miyake, circa 1971-1980
    Bulk is material relating to several Issey Miyake fashion shows directed by Ishioka, including the Issey Miyake Show (1975), Issey Miyake and 12 Black Women (1976), and Fly with Issey Miyake (1977). Material consists of photographs, snapshots, transparencies, contact sheets, and posters. Also present are items pertaining to a store display and textiles designed for Miyake by Ishioka, as well as event snapshots and publicity. See Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
    See Series 7 for material relating to magazine fashion spreads highlighting Miyake that were art directed by Ishioka.
    - Store display: photographs, undated (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Store display: photographs, slides, transparencies, undated (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - Fashion shoot: photographs, circa 1975-1977 (Box 147, Folder 13-14, Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Fashion shows: photographs, circa 1975-1977 (Box 148, Folder 2-6, Box 158, Folder 2-8, Box 159, Folder 2-3)
      There are several sets of photographs. Some sets also include fashion shoots.
    - Fashion shows: signed photographs, 1975, circa 1976 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Fashion shows: slides, transparencies, negatives, circa 1975-1977 (Box 436, Box 437, Box 438, Box 439, Box 440, Box 443, Box 466, Folder 1)
    - Fashion shows: contact sheets, circa 1975-1977 (Box 159, Folder 5-8, Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Fashion shows: Fly with Issey Miyake souvenir booklet, 1977 (Box 178)
    - Fashion shows: posters, circa 1975-1977 (Box 11, Box 18, Box 19)
      Includes Issey Miyake (box 11), Issey Miyake Show (two variations, box 11), Issey Miyake and 12 Black Women (Parco, box 18), and Fly with Issey Miyake (Parco, box 19).
    - Fashion shows: poster production material, undated (Box 50)
    - Textile design: samples and sketches (designs by Ishioka), circa 1971 (Box 207, Folder 7, Box 208, Box 209, Box 210)
    - Textile design: photographs, slides, transparencies, circa 1971 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Miyake birthday party: photographs, undated (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Miyake event: photographs, 1980 (Box 715, Folder 7-10)
      For images of other events attended by Miyake, see Series 12, Subseries 12.6.